lamar.edu 2004-12-06

# Lamar University: Contact LU

**  
Privacy Policy**

Lamar University respects your privacy. The University's main website, located at http://www.lamar.edu and all pages that begin with that address, follow this privacy policy.

**Cookies**  
Our main website does not collect personal information about visitors. Specifically, we do not use "cookies" to collect information. However, faculty and staff at Lamar who are updating their committee meeting minutes via the Faculty/Staff website are required to accept cookies as part of the login process. This cookie contains the username, password, and committee identification and does not contain any other information. 

Additionally, current students who wish to post messages in the message forums in the LUforStudents section are also required to accept cookies to post information. This cookie contains username, posting privelege level, and information denoting whether or not the Terms and Conditions have been read. This information is not used for any purpose other than to facilitate use of the message forums, and it will not be made available to anyone outside the web services department. If you are a current student of Lamar University, and you object to accepting cookies, you must refrain from using the message forums. Please read the Terms and Conditions of the message forums for more information.

**Personal Information**  
Personal information that is provided voluntarily to the University through use of email or online forms is used solely for the purpose of assisting you, such as servicing requests for information, responding to inquiries, or resolving technical problems with the website. Requests or inquiries may be forwarded to parties with Lamar University who can better service you.

You are entitled to the following, regarding personal information that may be collected about you:

1) On request, to be informed about the information that Lamar University collects about you;  
2) To receive and review the information; and  
3) To have Lamar University correct information about you that is incorrect.

We do use server logs to collect general information regarding your Internet connection and your visit to our website. This information is compiled and viewed in summarized form to analyze trends, target problem areas, and affect design or technical aspects of the site. Specific information about any one connection to our website will only be provided when legally required to assist law enforcement investigations.

Websites on other servers at Lamar University (such as http://hal.lamar.edu) may use cookies and/or collect personal information about you and use it in ways other than stated above. Each website that collects information will provide its own privacy policy and disclose their uses of your information.

If you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, the practices of this or other Lamar University websites, or your use of this site, please contact the webmaster at [webmaster@lamar.edu](mailto:webmaster@lamar.edu) , or through postal mail at:

Office of Information Technologies  
Attn: Webmaster  
P.O. Box 10020  
Beaumont, Texas 77710
